<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep-learning on Tanay Kumar Saha</title>
    <link>https://tksaha.github.io/tags/deep-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep-learning on Tanay Kumar Saha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Tanay Kumar Saha</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tksaha.github.io/tags/deep-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning of Network Units</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-netunit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-netunit/</guid>
      <description>In classical machine learning, hand-designed features are used for learning a mapping from the features. However, recently, there is a surge of research in representation learning which aims to learn abstract features given the input. For networks, representation learned for nodes and edges has been used for tasks, such as link prediction, collective classification, and many others. In my PhD thesis, I have crafted methods for learning representation for both the sentences and the network nodes/edges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning of Textual Units</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-text/</guid>
      <description>In classical machine learning, hand-designed features are used for learning a mapping from the features. However, recently, there is a surge of research in representation learning which aims to learn abstract features given the input. For textual domain, representation learning focuses on learning important semantic information from words, phrases, sentences or any arbitrary unit of texts, such as paragraphs and documents. The learned representation can be used in various data mining tasks, such as classification, clustering, summarization and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>