<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nlp on Tanay Kumar Saha</title>
    <link>https://tksaha.github.io/tags/nlp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nlp on Tanay Kumar Saha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Tanay Kumar Saha</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tksaha.github.io/tags/nlp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning of Textual Units</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-text/</guid>
      <description>In classical machine learning, hand-designed features are used for learning a mapping from the features. However, recently, there is a surge of research in representation learning which aims to learn abstract features given the input. For textual domain, representation learning focuses on learning important semantic information from words, phrases, sentences or any arbitrary unit of texts, such as paragraphs and documents. The learned representation can be used in various data mining tasks, such as classification, clustering, summarization and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Recall</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/totalrecall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/totalrecall/</guid>
      <description>Total Recall is an important task in supervised text mining. The objective of this task is to find everything about an entity or about a research question. For example, in Technology assisted review (TAR), the objective is to find all the documents relevant to a request for production in a legal matter, whereas, Systematic Review (SR) involves formulating a research question, searching in multiple biomedical databases, identifying relevant Randomized Control Trails (RCTs) based on abstracts and titles (abstract screening) and then based on full texts of a subset thereof, assessing their methodological qualities, extracting different data elements and synthesize them, and finally reporting the conclusions on a particular review question.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>