<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Tanay Kumar Saha</title>
    <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Tanay Kumar Saha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Tanay Kumar Saha</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tksaha.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Name Disambiguation</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/name-disambiguation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/name-disambiguation/</guid>
      <description>Entity disambiguation is not a new problem. In fact, named entity disambiguation has been a long standing problem in the field of bibliometrics and library science. The key reason for this is that many distinct authors share the same name, specifically considering the fact that the first name of an author is typically written in abbreviated form in the citation of many scientific journals. Thus, bibliographic servers that maintain such data may mistakenly aggregate the records from different persons into a single entity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Analysis and Mining</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/netanalysis-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/netanalysis-mining/</guid>
      <description>The main objective of Frequent Subgraph Mining (FSM) is finding subgraph patterns that are frequent across a collection of graphs. Another important task is to find subgraphs which are candidate for motif in a given network. For this, we need to count each topology&amp;rsquo;s frequency in the input network as well as in many randomized networks. Counting a topology&amp;rsquo;s frequency in a single network is a challenging task as it requires solving subgraph isomorphism, a known $NP$-complete problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning of Network Units</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-netunit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-netunit/</guid>
      <description>In classical machine learning, hand-designed features are used for learning a mapping from the features. However, recently, there is a surge of research in representation learning which aims to learn abstract features given the input. For networks, representation learned for nodes and edges has been used for tasks, such as link prediction, collective classification, and many others. In my PhD thesis, I have crafted methods for learning representation for both the sentences and the network nodes/edges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning of Textual Units</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/representation-text/</guid>
      <description>In classical machine learning, hand-designed features are used for learning a mapping from the features. However, recently, there is a surge of research in representation learning which aims to learn abstract features given the input. For textual domain, representation learning focuses on learning important semantic information from words, phrases, sentences or any arbitrary unit of texts, such as paragraphs and documents. The learned representation can be used in various data mining tasks, such as classification, clustering, summarization and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Recall</title>
      <link>https://tksaha.github.io/project/totalrecall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tksaha.github.io/project/totalrecall/</guid>
      <description>Total Recall is an important task in supervised text mining. The objective of this task is to find everything about an entity or about a research question. For example, in Technology assisted review (TAR), the objective is to find all the documents relevant to a request for production in a legal matter, whereas, Systematic Review (SR) involves formulating a research question, searching in multiple biomedical databases, identifying relevant Randomized Control Trails (RCTs) based on abstracts and titles (abstract screening) and then based on full texts of a subset thereof, assessing their methodological qualities, extracting different data elements and synthesize them, and finally reporting the conclusions on a particular review question.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>